# Dontsov Maxim Pavlovich

Phone: +7-902-266-23-44
Email: <a href="mailto:frayneqt@gmail">frayneqt@gmail</a>
Telegram: <a href="mailto:@MoreAllMaxx">@MoreAllMaxx</a>
City: Yekaterinburg

Date of Birth: 20.08.1994

# Python-developer / Django-developer

## **Skills**

Python 3.9, aiogram, numpy, PyQT, Pygame, unittest, Django, HTML/CSS, bootstrap-grids, databases via ORM, can work with many Python libraries and programming technologies.

# Work experience

#### **Freelance**

August 2021 - February 2022

# **Python developer**

I have developed on freelance:

- telegram bots using the aiogram library;
- services for collecting data;
- E-Mailing Services;
- Django Applications;
- automated tests for finished projects;
- adding the functionality of the async library to existing projects.

#### **Urals Optical & Mechanical Plant**

Yekaterinburg, www.uomz.com June 2020 — October 2021

#### **Development engineer (designer)**

Development and support of serial production of products:

- implementation of design preparation for the production of blocks and assemblies on printed circuit boards in terms of drawings, parts, assembly units;
- development of software in microcircuits of blocks (languages C, Assembler);
- development of design documentation for printed circuit assemblies and electronic components.

# **Dontsov Maxim Pavlovich**

Phone: +7-902-266-23-44
Email: <a href="mailto:frayneqt@gmail">frayneqt@gmail</a>
Telegram: <a href="mailto:@MoreAllMaxx">@MoreAllMaxx</a>
City: Yekaterinburg

Date of Birth: 20.08.1994

# **Work experience (continued)**

## **Velo-City**

Yekaterinburg

March 2020 - August 2020

## **Development engineer (electronic engineer)**

Development of a bike sharing system:

- design of a bicycle parking station with an electronic lock, charging for batteries on a bicycle - a control board, sensors, system power, the ability to connect additional stations;
- bicycle control unit control board, sensors, user interaction through the display, power distribution of various bicycle systems;
- software development for control systems: Python, C, C++ languages with the Wiring framework.

#### **Ural Works of Civil Aviation**

Yekaterinburg, www.uwca.ru

August 2019 — January 2020

#### **Development engineer (designer)**

Development and support of the production of the power supply system and the instrument panel of civil aircraft:

- electrical circuits;
- printed circuit boards;
- electronic blocks.
- design documentation.

September 2018 — August 2019

## **Process Engineer**

Organization of a workshop for the assembly of on-board radio-electronic equipment.

Selection of components for radio electronic products.

Organization and adjustment of the test site.

Development and implementation of technological documentation.

Accompanying pilot and then serial production.

# Dontsov Maxim Pavlovich

Phone: +7-902-266-23-44
Email: <a href="mailto:frayneqt@gmail">frayneqt@gmail</a>
Telegram: <a href="mailto:@MoreAllMaxx">@MoreAllMaxx</a>
City: Yekaterinburg

Date of Birth: 20.08.1994

## **Education**

#### **Higher technical**

# Ural Federal University named after the first President of Russia B.N. Yeltsin, Yekaterinburg

Optical technologies and materials, 2018

# **Courses and Trainings**

#### **SKILLBOX**

Python Developer from Scratch, Django, Web Development, 2021

# Ural Federal University named after the first President of Russia B.N. Yeltsin, Yekaterinburg

Department of Foreign Languages, Translation of technical and business documentation in English, 2017

## **Additional Information**

Driving license - category B. Russian language is native.

English language is conversational, also I can read technical literature.

## **About me**

I am ready to become a part of an IT team that will benefit from my programming knowledge and experience, teamwork experience, as well as the thinking of a development engineer.

I approach work proactively and responsibly: for example, when working on a large task, I divide it into smaller parts, independently plan tasks and their priority, try to meet deadlines and am open to constructive feedback.

My strengths include the experience of working in a team, the desire to find the most effective and beautiful solution, the ability to independently search for resources that help solve a problem or improve my professional level.